the year 2030
2030年
Kids,back in 2009,your Aunt Robin was
孩子们 2009年那会儿 你们Robin阿姨
the host of a morning show for local New York cable.
在纽约地方有线台主持一档早间节目
come on get up new york!
早哇 纽约!
And it was on early. How early?
而且还挺早的 有多早?
Mike? wakey,wakey.
Mike? 醒醒
But then,everything changed.
但之后 一切都不同了
See my show?
有看我的节目吗?
Oh,I meant to watch it.
噢 我本来想看的
I just got so busy with the whole "being sound asleep" thing.
不过我忙着睡觉 腾不出时间
It took all night,eight hours down the drain.
花了我整晚功夫 八个小时就这么没了
Oh,it's fine. But get this:
呃 没关系 你听着:
After the broadcast...
我做完节目后...
- Are you Robin? - Yeah.
- Robin是吗? - 是我
I'm Don,your new co-host.
我叫Don 是你的新同事
Don was Don Frank,seasoned veteran of no fewer than
Don全名Don Frank 曾活跃在全国
39 local morning news teams from all over the country.
不下于39个地方早间新闻的老面孔
The guy was an industry legend.
这家伙就是传说中的哥
You are so going to hit that.
你有很大机会拿下他哦
No,I just think we're going to be great together on the air.
不是 我只是想工作时我们会很融洽
And on the sofa and on the bed and on the coffee table.
并且在沙发 床上和咖啡桌上也很"融洽"
All right,all right.
好啦
I'm gonna go up on the roof and stand there by myself for five minutes.
我要上天台 自己小站个五分钟
Have fun.
好好玩
And that's exactly what she did.
就是这样
She just stood there.
她就这么站在那里
All right,kids,I'm gonna level with you.
好吧 孩子们 我说实话
That's not what she did.
她没那么做
Here's what she did.
这才是她真正所为
All right,all right.
好啦
- I'm going to go have a cigarette. - What?!
- 我上去抽根烟 - 什么?!
I promised her I'd never tell you this,
我跟她保证过不告诉你们的
but once upon a time, your Aunt Robin did enjoy the occasional cigarette,
很久之前 你们Robin阿姨偶尔会抽抽烟
and occasionally that occasional cigarette...
而这个"偶尔"
was more than just occasional.
偶尔会超出"偶尔"的定义
I just left something like this in my apartment.
我家现在也有这么一玩意儿
Robin,come on,take it to the roof.
Robin 别这样 上天台抽呀
We said no smoking in the apartment
之前你做掌上压烧掉了地毯
after you torched the throw rug doing push-ups.
我就跟你说过 室内不准吸烟
All right,all right,all right. Geez.
好啦好啦 唠叨
Yeah,Robin,I mean,God,not only is that a filthy habit,
就是 Robin 天 这不单单是个坏习惯
but also,can I bum one?
而且 给我一支好吗?
- Sure. - What?!
- 没问题 - 什么?!
how i met your mother  s05e11</font
老爸老妈的罗曼史 第五季 第11集
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- Sync: 卡灰
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: HOLAH 化竹梗 校对: 代班草儿 时间轴: 卡灰
Kids,your Uncle Marshall definitely doesn't want you to know this,
孩子们 Marshall叔叔不想让你们知道
but he also smoked off and on.
但他也会偶尔吸烟
It all started when he was 13,on a camping trip in Minnesota.
故事发生在他13岁 是在明尼苏达州露营
Come on,Marshall,let's celebrate. It's summer vacation.
来嘛 Marshall 庆祝一下 难得的暑假
Okay,but just one.
好吧 就一支
This is my first and last cigarette ever.
这是我第一支 同时也是最后一支烟
And that was the first of many,many "last cigarettes ever.
而那只是众多"最后一支烟"中的第一次
" That's it. I am done,I am out.
够了 我要戒烟
Last... Cigarette... ...ev-arrh!
这是我... 最后... ...一支烟!
So,by that point,I'd heard it all before.
所以 那时 他说的都是以前的陈词滥调
Last cigaretteever.
最后一支烟
What are you doing? You haven't smoked in six months.
你怎么了? 你已经六个月没碰烟了
Is this about the McRib?
是不是因为麦当劳猪扒堡?
It's gone,dude,let it go.
它都被撤出菜单了 就让它过去吧
I'm worried about work,okay?
是因为工作
They just hired a new head of the legal department,
法律部来了个新头头
and he's going to be letting people go.
他可是会裁员的
So that's why you're worried?
你就担心这个?
The new head of the legal department is Arthur Hobbes.
法律部的新头头是Arthur Hobbes
As in "Artillery Arthur"?
就是那个"大炮嘴Arthur"?
As in your former boss?
你以前的上司?
Arthur Hobbes was the meanest boss Marshall or anyone else had ever had.
不仅仅是Marshall Arthur Hobbes 绝对是每个人遇过最刻薄的上司
The last time Marshall worked for him,it ended like this.
以前Marshall在他手底下工作 最后变成这样
I quit!
老子不干了!
Yikes.
恐怖
So does he hold it against you?
就这件事 他给你小鞋穿了?
Worse.
宁愿这样
I'm sorry,who are you?
不好意思 你哪位?
I'm,I'm Marshall Eriksen.
我是Marshall Eriksen
- Um,we had a fairly intense screaming match. - No.
- 我们曾经大吵过一架 - 没记忆
Wherein I suggested that you take your head
其中 我曾建议过您把脑袋摘下
and store it within yourself in a fashion that,
在身体里找一地方藏好
while,while space-saving,might limit its exposure to,to sunshine.
即能有效利用空间 又能避免阳光直射 (就是塞菊花里咯 真隐晦...)
Well,that describes 95% of my employees and everyone in my family...
跟我手下95%的员工和我家里人很像...
except for my dog.
除了我的狗
He's such a good boy.
真是个好小伙
Well... I'll see you later,uh...
晚点见吧 呃...
Randall Wilkerson.
Randall Wilkerson
Marshall Eriksen.
Marshall Eriksen
Gary Dinkersfield,right.
Gary Dinkersfield 没错
Great,he doesn't remember you.
好哇 他不记得你了
Not great. Arthur Hobbes hating Marshall--
不好 Arthur Hobbes讨厌Marshall--
that's no big deal. He hates everyone.
那只是小事 他讨厌所有人
It's the people he doesn't know that he cuts loose.
他专炒他不认识的人
He just fired What's-His-Face.
他刚炒了 那谁谁
He fired What's- His-Face,Ted,and What's-His-Face was invaluable.
他炒了那谁谁 Ted 那谁谁很能干的
Look,I can understand you getting upset,
你这么担忧我很理解
but it's not worth killing yourself over.
但为此慢性自杀就不值得了
Yeah,wait till you get laid off,then kill yourself.
等你被炒鱿鱼了 再自杀
Like What's-His-Face.
就像那谁谁
Although I guess now it's more like Where's-His-Face.
不过我想现在更应该是"那碎碎"了 (跳楼自杀!?)
Look,it was just two cigarettes.
就两根烟
Okay,I can handle two.
两支没问题的
As long as I don't have three within 24 hours,
只要在24小时内不吸第三支
then I'm not going to get hooked again.
那我就不会上瘾
What's Lily going to say when she finds out you smoked?
要是被Lily发现你吸烟怎么办?
Lily's not going to find out.
Lily不会发现啦
I have a system.
哥自有一套法子
Ah,yes,Marshall's system.
没错 Marshall大法
- Hey,Lil. - You smoked.
- 嘿 Lil - 你吸烟了
Damn it!
可恶!
The next morning,your Aunt Robin was thrilled
第二天早上 你们Robin阿姨很兴奋
to be finally going on the air with a real pro.
她终于可以跟一位真正专业人士合作
In three,two,one...
三 二 一...
Hi,I'm Robin Scherbatsky.
大家好 我是Robin Scherbatsky
AndI... am Don Frank.
我...是Don Frank
Two teens were arrested late last night for stealing a police cart.
两名少年昨夜因 偷窃一部警用手推车被捕
No,I'm sorry,not a police cart,a policecar.
不好意思 不是警用手推车 是警车
Aw,screw it.
随便啦
Brain fart.
脑子进水啦
Don't you hate those?
真讨厌是吧?
Oh,look at that,the teleprompter's still running.
看 讲词提示机还在显示呢
Something about a woman giving birth on an uptown bus.
貌似有个女人在小区巴士上生小孩
Well,no point in jumping in halfway.
那是 你总不能中途跳出车吧
I'll just wait till it's done.
要我就等完事再下车
and she cut the cord with a Metropass.
而她还用地铁月票割开脐带
We'll be right back.
稍后请继续收看
And we're clear.
搞定
What the hell was that?
刚才怎么回事?
Don,you said "brain fart.
Don 你说"脑子进水"
" Look,Robin,you seem like a nice kid,but this is my 39th local news show,okay?
这样 Robin 看来你是个乖孩子 不过这是我第39个地方新闻节目
And in that time,I've learned three things:
从中 我学到三样东西:
avoid the all-you-can-eat sushi buffet in Bismarck,
不要去俾斯麦 任何一间任吃寿司自助餐
do not go to the bathroom with your lapel mic still on,
微型麦克风还开着时 不要去洗手间
and three,at this hour,your entire viewing audience
第三 此时你的所有观众
is one half-drunk slob sitting in his underwear,so...
只是些喝得半醉的大汉 只穿着内裤 所以...
Back in five,four...
五 四 ...
Well,let's do a great show for that half-drunk slob.
那我们就为了那些醉汉做好节目吧
Well,that half-drunk slob appreciates it.
醉汉会感激你的
The next day,Marshall found himself craving a cigarette.
第二天Marshall发现自己烟瘾犯了
It was driving him crazy,so he decided to get some fresh air.
让他很难受 所以他决定上天台透透气
Oh,no. You're not up here to jump,are you?
不是吧 你不是上来跳楼的吧?
- No,no,no,no. - I fired a lot of people today.
- 不 不是 - 我今天炒了不少人
I don't need another jumper in my file.
我可不想档案里再加个再次害人跳楼了
Oh,uh,cigarette?
来一根?
No,no,thank you.
不了 谢谢
That's too bad.
真可惜
You know what I miss,Jeffrey?
真怀念以前 知道是什么吗? Jeffrey
Getting to know somebody over a smoke.
从吸烟打屁中了解对方
People are so interchangeable now,
现在的人都太善变了
but you share a butt with somebody,you got a real bond.
不过要是大家一起吸过烟 那就是哥们
You know what? I will,I will take one.
我 我还是来一根吧
Okay. Thank you.
谢谢
I'm Marshall,by the way,it's Marshall,Marshall Eriksen.
我叫Marshall 顺便 我叫Marshall Marshall Eriksen
Yeah. Tell me something,Marshall Eriksen.
告诉我Marshall Eriksen
How would you like to see a picture of the cutest dog in the world?
要不要看看世上最可爱的狗狗?
There he is. He's a good boy.
就是他 好小伙
You smoked.
你抽烟了
S Yes,I smoked,and it was my third of the day.
没错我抽烟了 而且是我今天第三根
You know what that means? I'm a smoker now. It's all over.
知道那代表什么? 我现在是个烟民 全完了
I even bought a pack on the way home
回家时我甚至还买了一包
and a lighter and a Vikings lamp,
还有打火机 和Vikings的台灯
which has nothing to do with anything, but I saw it in the window and I liked it.
虽然没什么关系 不过我路过窗边看见 很喜欢
Damn it,Marshall.
可恶 Marshall
We already have four Viking lamps and smoking kills.
家里已经有四个Viking台灯和戒烟贴了
It was a way to bond with my boss,okay?
我只是想藉此跟上司打好关系
You should have seen me up there.
你都没见我做了什么
- That is a cute dog. - Yeah.
- 这狗真可爱 - 是啊
- Are those your kids? - Yeah,yeah,whatever.
- 那些是你孩子? - 是吧 随便吧
Hey,oh,look what I got at the mall.
这是我从商场买的
There he is. There he is.
就是他 就是他
- Go ahead,you can pet him now. - No.
- 来 拍拍他的头 - 不了
Yeah,yeah,come on,he likes it.
来嘛 他很喜欢的
Scratch him under the chin.
逗逗他的下巴
I don't care what your reasons are.
我不管你什么理由
You know how I feel about smoking.
你知道我对吸烟什么看法的
Now,give me the cigarettes.
香烟给我
And the lighter.
还有打火机
Ah,that's the stuff.
爽死了
- What?! - Oh,yeah,add your Aunt Lily to the list.
- 什么?! - 没错 你们Lily阿姨也是烟鬼
Whenever Uncle Marshall fell off the wagon,
不管Marshall叔叔做什么
your Aunt Lily got dragged right down with him.
你们Lily阿姨总是嫁鸡随鸡 嫁狗随狗
What you doing?
你在干嘛?
If you must know,I am reaching out to City Hall
要是你真要知道 我在跟市政厅联系
to try to get the mayor on our show.
看能不能请市长过来做节目
Oh,my goodness,you are adorable,
我的天 你真可爱
but the mayor's not coming on a show nobody watches.
不过要是节目没观众 市长才不会来呢
My colonoscopy had more viewers than this show.
我做个结肠镜检查都比这节目观众多
At least that had some twists and turns.
起码那内窥镜还比较峰回路转呢
You know,I don't,I don't know why you're acting like this.
我不知道你为什么会这样
Maybe you're just bitter because you ne ver had a shot at a network job,
你这么刻薄可能是 因为你没机会爬上电视网工作
but I think I still do,so I really need to focus.
但我认为我还有希望 所以我要专心
I've been on a network.
我在电视网做过
You were on a network?
你在电视网做过?
It was the best Labor Day weekend of my life.
那是我一生中最棒的劳动节假期
When you do the news,you're in these ergonomic chairs.
你坐着完全符合人体工学的椅子做新闻
It feels like you're sitting on a cloud.
就好像坐在云端一样
Which was nice 'cause it was right after my colonoscopy.
感觉很棒 因为我刚做完结肠镜检查
And the dressing rooms?
还有化妆间
There's dressing rooms?
那里有化妆间?
Oh,you bet your sweet headset there's dressing rooms,Mike.
以你那可爱的耳机起誓 那里当然有化妆间 Mike
No changing in the KFC bathroom across the street.
与街边KFC一模一样的洗手间
No,sir.
完全一模一样
CB SIt was heaven.
那就是天堂
But the second you get used to it,
一旦你已经习惯之后
they go find someone who isn't "going through a bitter divorce"
他们就会找个没有"离婚烦恼"
and doesn't "reek of gin,"
或者不是"一身酒气"的人来代替你
and before you know it,you're stuck in a dead-end gig,
最后你发现 你被困在个没出路的节目
surrounded by people going nowhere,doing the news in your tighty whities.
周围都是无所事事的人 穿着紧身白内裤做新闻
Okay,the underwear thing was your choice,
这样 穿内裤是你自己的问题
and I don't like that it's catching on.
而且我搞不明白为什么就流行起来了
Ah,looking good,fellas.
啊 帅啊 兄弟
Feels good,right?
感觉不错是吧?
God,I want to kill him.
我真想干掉他
Of course people watch the show.
当然有人看我的节目
You guys watch the show,that's,like,two right there.
你们会看我的节目 这样就有两个
Oh,my God.
不是吧
You guys still haven't seen my show.
你们居然还没看过我的节目
- What? We never miss it. - We've seen it!
- 什么? 我们每集必追的 - 我们看过!
Really? What color is the set?
真的? 背景是什么颜色?
- It's black. - Right. Yeah.
- 黑色 - 没错
- With,like,silver Uh-huh. around the edges. - Yeah.
- 有银色的边缘 - 是啊
Not your TV set,my show set.
不是电视的背景 是摄影场的背景
God,if I can't even get my best friends to watch,who's going to watch?
要是我的好朋友都不看 那还有谁会看?
Lots of people.
有好多人会看
Uh,you got bedridden insomniacs.
卧床不起的失眠症患者
Bums camping outside a department store.
在百货商店外扎营的流浪汉
People waiting in the ER,where the TV is in a cage,
在急症室外等候的人 那里的电视机放在架子上
so you can't change the channel.
你没法换频道
Ooh,do you have any stalkers?
你有粉丝吗?
Yeah,but even Leonard won't watch my show.
嗯 但是连Leonard都不看我的节目
I can't believe those guys are smoking out there.
真不敢相信他们在外面抽烟
It's freezing out.
外面冷死了
Remember when you used to be able to smoke in bars?
还记得那时候你在酒吧里吸烟吗?
Oh,hey,dude. I think that hot girl over there's smiling at me.
嘿 哥们 我觉得那边的辣妹在朝我笑
Uh,that's a chair. But yeah,dude,hit that.
那是个椅子 不过去上吧
Guys?
伙计们?
Marco!
Polo!
Polo! (Marco Polo游泳池里的游戏)
Well,it's dividing our group into smokers and non-smokers.
它把我们分割成吸烟者和非吸烟者
And that's not healthy.
加之吸烟有害健康
You're right.
说得对
Let's go have a smoke.
我们去抽烟吧
What?!
啥?!
Yeah,I'm not proud of it.
我不是引以为傲
Look at you two. Smokers.
瞧瞧你俩 烟鬼
Just like the rest of us.
跟我们一样
I am not a smoker.
我可不是烟鬼
I only smoke in certain situations.
我只是在特定情况下才吸烟
Postcoital,when I'm with Germans--
嘿咻后 和德国佬一起时
sometimes those two overlap--
有时这两者交叉
coital,birthdays,to annoy my mom,
嘿咻时 生日时 惹我妈生气时
precoital,on a sailboat,
嘿咻前 在帆船上时
the day the Mets are mathematically eliminated every year,and,of course--
每年大都会队惨遭淘汰的那天 还有
wait for it,'cause Lord knows I have--
等一下 天知道我为啥有
pregnancy scares.
怀孕恐惧症
Why are you smoking right now?
那你现在为啥抽烟?
I'm always precoital,Ted.
我一直处于嘿咻前 Ted
You know,maybe smoking's not so bad.
也许抽烟没那么糟
I mean,at least it gets us out in the fresh air.
我是说 至少能让我们 出来呼吸新鲜空气
Yeah,and all the coughing really works my abs.
嗯 咳嗽能锻炼腹肌
I... am... ripped!
我...好...健美!
But,as glamorous as it was,within a week,we all hit our breaking point.
尽管欲罢不能 不过一周后 我们都几乎崩溃
You okay,sweetie?
你没事吧 宝贝?
Actually,baby,my throat's a bit sore.
宝贝 其实我的喉咙有点痛
three flights later...
三层楼梯后
- So,I'm whapping him across the nose with the newspaper,right? - Yeah.
- 我用报纸猛他耳光 对吧? - 嗯
And my wife says,"Come on,you can't treat your son like that.
我老婆说"住手 你不能这样对待自己儿子"
" I don't know.
我不清楚
Michael,call 911. Oh...
Michael 打911
oh,my God. Okay,yes,yeah,right away.
我的天 好好 马上
It's Marshall,by the way.
顺带一提 我是Marshall
Oh,my God. I hope Arthur's okay.
我的天 希望Arthur没事
Dibs on his office if he's not.
要是他出事 他的办公室就归我了
We have to quit smoking.
我们得戒烟
Honey,you said a mouthful.
亲爱的 你说得对
I wish I had never started.
真希望我从没上手过
I mean,I think back to myself at 13 years old.
我想回到13岁那会儿
If I could only go back to that moment...
要是能回到那时候
I hate that little bastard.
我恨那只小赤佬
Me,too.
我也是
Okay,that's it. Let's quit.
好吧 就这么办 我们戒烟
Let's... Let's do it.
我们戒烟
Well,I am proud of you guys.
我真为你们感到自豪
I have heard how difficult it is for smokers like yourself to quit,
我听说过像你们这样的烟民 戒烟有多难
so,on behalf of nonsmokers,I salute you,and I am here to help.
我代表不吸烟的同志向你们致敬 同时我在这里提供帮助
So,hand in your cigarettes,and I will get rid of them one at a time.
所以上交你们的烟  我会一根一根地扔掉
You're quitting,dollface.
你也戒烟 萝莉脸
I know I don't normally call you dollface,
我知道我通常不叫你萝莉脸
but it kind of works in this voice.
但用这嗓子说真有味
Dollface.
萝莉脸
- Hey,guys. - Hey.
- 嘿 各位 - 嘿
Uh,I was just wondering,um,is anyone else
我想知道明天还有谁会
interviewing the mayor tomorrow on TV,or is it just me?
在电视上采访市长? 除了我之外
Hey,that's great.
嘿 真棒
Yeah,Don can suck it while I suck this.
我出风头的时候 Don就一边凉快去吧
Light me,Marshall.
帮我点上 Marshall
Actually,um,we've decided that we're all quitting smoking.
其实我们都决定戒烟了
That's fantastic.
妙极
I'm sick of you guys bumming my cigarettes.
我很讨厌你们老揩油我的烟
No,come on,Robin. We-we can't do it unless we all do it together.
拜托 Robin 要是不同心协力 我们就戒不了烟
No.
不行
You can sleep with Marshall.
你可以和Marshall上床
Oh,God,Lily,no.
我的妈 Lily 别啊
Sorry,baby,you got to take one for the team.
抱歉 宝贝 你得为团队牺牲一下
I-I don't want to sleep with Marshall.
我才不想和Marshall上床
- I've seen the looks. - Right.
- 我能从表情上得知 - 对的
I can't quit right now.
我现在没法戒
Not before the biggest interview of my life.
在一生中最重要的采访之前 戒不了
It's-it's too stressful.
压力太大了
It's too stressful!
- Let's just have one more. - Give me a cigarette!!
- 再抽一根 - 给我烟!!
No,wait! Robin,Robin,think about this for a second.
不 等下! Robin Robin 仔细想想
Bloomberg is the antismoking mayor.
Bloomberg市长提倡禁烟
Do you really want to show up to that interview smelling like smoke?
你想采访的时候满身烟味吗?
It'd be like interviewing a vegetarian smelling like a McRib.
就象采访满身猪排堡味的素食主义者
Really? Like I'm not going through enough right now?
是吗? 那我现在不能抽到爽了?
Look,you're quitting. We're all quitting.
听着 你要戒烟 我们都要戒烟
Fine. I'll quit.
好吧 我戒
Great. Great. We just have to get through the first 24 hours.
很好 我们只要熬过24小时
After that,it's a cakewalk.
之后就小菜一碟了
26 hours later
26小时后
Barney,do you have to bite your nails so loud?
Barney 你有必要把指甲啃那么响吗?
I'm not biting my nails.
我不是在啃指甲
I'm trying to suck the leftover nicotine out of my fingertips.
我在用力吸指尖残留的尼古丁
Marshall,can you pass the onion rings?
Marshall 你能递一下洋葱圈吗?
What,you got dinosaur arms? They're right there.
咋 你是恐龙爪子吗? 它们就在这儿
What do you think cigarettes are doing right now?
你们觉得香烟这会在做啥呢?
You think they're thinking about us?
你们觉得它们在想我们吗?
Dude,if you don't stop tapping your foot,it's coming off.
老兄 你的腿再抖就散架了
Oh,my God,Ted,I'm so sorry.
我的天哪 Ted 真对不起
Maybe I should move it a little bit closer to your ass!
看来我该往你臀部踹上两脚!
All right. I am ready to do this right now!
好吧 我现在就想动手了!
None of us knew what we were fighting about.
鬼才知道我们在吵啥
We just knew we wanted to smoke.
我们只想抽一口
More than anything in the world.
别无他求
It wasn't going very well for Robin,either.
Robin也同样不好过
Sorry I'm late.
抱歉我迟到了
Someone used the microwave,and the elevator stopped.
有人用微波炉 所以电梯停了
- What are you doing? - Okay,Don,Don,seriously,not tonight.
- 在干吗呢? - Don 说真的 今晚安分点
Okay,I'm a little bit on edge because I quit smoking for my interview with the mayor,so just...
我有些烦躁 为了采访市长 我把烟戒了 所以...
Oh,you precious little porcelain unicorn,you.
你还真稀世罕见的小怪胎
Why would you do that?
你为啥要这么做?
Why?! Because I care,Don.
为什么?! 因为我在乎 Don
I-I care about the show,I-I care about my career.
我在意这个节目 我在意我的工作
Unlike you,you unprofessional jerk!
不象你 混日子的喽!
You're-You're sloppy,you're rude,
你 你又邋遢又粗鲁
and I wish you worked half as hard as
你要是有弹力三角裤上
the elastic on those stretched-out underpants.
橡皮筋的一半努力就好了
I'm starting to feel like this is getting a little personal.
我觉得这有点人身攻击的味道
No,Don,it would be getting personal
不 Don 如果我说
if I would say that the reason you bounce
你老是从东家换到西家的原因
from market to market is because you're a loser--
是因为你是个败类
a lazy,obnoxious,loser.
懒到生虫的可恨败类
The mayor canceled.
市长取消了
In five,four,three,two...
5 4 3 2...
Hi,I'm Robin Scherbatsky.
嗨 我是Robin Scherbatsky
You think I'm a loser?
你觉得我是败类?
You're' right. I'm a loser.
你说得对 我是败类
But at least I've accepted it.
但至少我敢于承认
A plucky raccoon has been cheering up patients at a local senior center.
一只勇敢浣熊在老人中心 给病人们带来欢乐
I used to be just like that.
我以前也像你一样
Always wanting more and never getting it.
期望着有所回报 但总是事与愿违
It's a dead end,Robin.
穷途末路了 Robin
You're never going to be a network anchor.
你永远成不了新闻联播主持人
Just like you're never going to quit smoking.
正如你永远戒不了烟一样
What are you doing?
你在干吗?
I'm enjoying a cigarette.
享受吞云吐雾的快感
Oh,that'll get you there.
喔 快活赛神仙
Oh,that's good.
感觉真妙
You want a drag?
来一口吗?
Can we be professionals? Please?
能专业点吗? 拜托?
Yeah. Yeah,professionals?
对对 专业?
You know who's working the camera right now?
你知道谁在摄像吗?
A chair.
一把椅子
We're on a show where we can't even get the cameraman to watch.
我们的节目甚至没有摄像师观看
That's why the mayor canceled,Robin.
所以市长取消采访 Robin
And that's why Mike is on a fried chicken run.
所以Mike溜出去吃炸鸡
And that's why you and I can enjoy a cigarette right here on the air.
所以我和你能在直播时抽烟
No,thank you.
不 谢了
Why?
为什么?
Because of our millions and millions of impressionable viewers?
因为我们数之不尽的敏感观众?
Okay...
好吧
If any impressionable viewers have a problem with this,please give us a call.
要是任何敏感的观众对此有意见 请拨打电话
The number's on the screen.
号码在屏幕上
Chirp,chirp? Chirp,chirp?
铃铃铃 铃铃铃?
Come on,Robin... live a little.
拜托 Robin...活出自我本色
Oh,that must be Mike. He always forgets-- extra crispy.
肯定是Mike 他老是忘记"劲脆鸡腿堡"
- Hello? - Robin,don't smoke that cigarette!
- 喂? - Robin 别抽那烟!
- Marshall?! - We're all watching and we're all very impressionable.
- Marshall?! - 我们都在看 还有我们都很敏感
And I swear to God,if you smoke that cigarette,we're all going to smoke.
我向毛主席发誓 要是你一抽 我们都会去抽
You... You guys are watching?
你们...你们在看?
We sure are,sweetheart,and you look fabulous.
当然啦 宝贝 你好美
Oh,you guys.
伙计们
You don't have to do this,Robin. You don't have to smoke.
你没必要这么做 Robin 你没必要抽
Resist it,honey.
忍住 亲爱的
Thanks for the call,guys.
谢谢你们的电话 伙计们
- Oh,she did it! - Good for her.
- 她忍住了! - 真好
We're not going to smoke.
我们不会抽烟的
I have a pack stashed up on the roof.
我在屋顶上藏了盒烟
Uh-oh. I'm awake. And I'm smoking!
我醒了 我抽着烟
Robin,you know how dangerous it is to wake a sleep smoker?
Robin 你知道吵醒睡着的烟民多危险吗?
- It's fine. - I bought a pack on my way home.
没关系啦 我在回家的路上也买了包
- Hey,great show,Robin. - Yeah.
- 嘿 节目真不错 Robin - 嗯
Yeah,but that Don guy,what a tool.
嗯 那个叫Don的家伙好蠢
Well,no,he actually apologized to me.
没 他已经向我道歉了
No,I mean when he stood up.
不是 我是说他站起来时
Those briefs were pretty revealing.
三角裤包裹下若隐若现
You should date that guy.
你该和他约会
Yeah. Not in this lifetime.
嗯 下辈子吧
They were dating within two months.
2个月内他们就约会了
But more on that later.
那是后话
Hey,guys,look,the sun's coming up.
嘿 瞧 太阳升起来了
You know what right now is a perfect time for?
你们知道现在做啥的最佳时机吗?
A last cigarette ever.
最后一支烟
No,I mean,a real last cigarette ever.
不是 我是说真正的最后一支烟
Damn it,let's do it.
我靠 大家来吧
Okay.
好吧
All right.
Last cigarette ever on,uh,on the count of three.
最后一支烟 数到3
- One... Two... - Three.
- 1...2... - 3...
****
之后我们都戒了一段时间
**** anyone's last cigarette
但那都不是我们的最后一支烟
we did eventually all quit smoking for real.
我们最终都彻底把烟戒了
Robin's last cigarette was in June 2013.
Robin的最后一支烟是在2013年6月
Barney's last cigarette was in March 2017.
Barney的最后一支烟是在2017年3月
Lily's last cigarette was the day she started trying to get pregnant.
Lily的最后一支烟是 在计划要宝宝的那天
And Marshall's last cigarette was the day his son was born.
Marshall的最后一支烟是在他儿子出生那天
And my last cigarette?
我的呢?
Two weeks into dating your mother.
是在和你们老妈约会2周后
And I never looked back.
我再也没有复吸
aaa
真抱歉揍了你一顿
bbb
作为弥补
ccc
我把这个送给你
ddd
哇 她好辣
eee
嗯 有朝一日你会娶她
fff
不可能
ggg
运气爆棚
hhh
就是说
iii
我进帐篷了
jjj
别 等下 别那么做
kkk
替我玩得愉快
how i met your mother  s05e11</font
老爸老妈的罗曼史 第五季 第11集
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- Sync: 卡灰
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: HOLAH 化竹梗 校对: 代班草儿 时间轴: 卡灰